Christopher Baker

Mobile Phone: 0422 937 089 Email: christopherglenbaker@gmail.com 60 Dobbs Street, Holland Park West QLD, 4121

Professional Summary

Second year Computer Science – Machine Learning student that has excellent management experience within organisations. Expert in casino operations with a complete understanding of how each process is used to create an enjoyable experience for customers and employees. Special skills working with employees to grow their fundamental understanding of the tasks required and create an increase in their potential. Proficient at reacting quickly and calmly in an emergency to protect companies and patrons alike. Thorough understanding of various organisations operations. Dedicated to developing a profound understanding of professional and technical skills.

Work Experience

President • Queensland Lacrosse Association

Jan. 2020 to Jan. 2022

- Oversee board operational planning, implementation of procedures and creation of policies.
- A Participate with the Australian Lacrosse Association's strategic planning and implementation.
- Drive growth through programs and development within Queensland.

Director of Development • Queensland Lacrosse Association

Jan. 2018 to Jan. 2020

- Participate with board operational planning, implementation of procedures and creation of policies.
- Evaluate league growth and increase registration numbers across Queensland.
- Oversee athletic development at all skill levels within Queensland.

Gaming Supervisor • Knighted Ventures

Dec. 2013 to Dec. 2014

- Recognized amongst peers as a strong team builder who utilized the various skills of each employee to create a motivational and innovative work environment.
- Committed to delivering a high level of customer service.
- Created and updated department work instructions and reports on a regular basis.
- Responsible for ensuring all California Department of Justice gaming guidelines were being followed.
- Coordinated daily cash reconciliation at a high-volume location.

Education and Certifications

University of Queensland, Saint Lucia, Queensland

Expected Graduation: July 2021

Graduated: May 2013

- Bachelor of Computer Science Machine Learning
- 2019 UQ Lacrosse Club President and Men's Team Head Coach

Santa Rosa Junior College, Santa Rosa, California

- Firefighter 1 Certificate
- EMR, EMT, First Aid

Technical Skills

Microsoft Word/Excel
Python/Java/SQL/MATLAB

Project Management

Professional Skills

- Excellent Communication Skills
- Customer Service Oriented
- Workload Planning

- Strong Interpersonal Skills
- Superior Organizational Ability
- Report Writing

- Team Leader
- Friendly Demeanor
- Relationship Building